nextgenwalkthroughs.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | WikiGameGuides.com

##    
Wiki Game Guides Privacy Statement

##  Effective 01/01/11

###  Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

###  The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Wiki Game Guides website. On some pages you can sign in to make comments, or participate in our online forums. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Email address Online Usernames (e.g. Xbox Live Gamertag)

We partner with third party ad networks and allow such networks to use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable data for targeting and serving ads. Users can opt-out of this behavioral targeting by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

###  The Way We Use Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We use email addresses to validate your account and e-mail you updates such as private messages. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

###  Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

###  Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13.

###  How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging on to your profile and updating your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

###  How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at wikigameguides at gmail dot com.
